Guide to the Pittsburgh Zionist District Records, 1945-1965 AIS.1968.12
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- ZOA Convention, August 30-September 3, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Lists- Convention, 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Annual Meeting, May 25, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 8-9)
- Social, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Publicity, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Purim Dance, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 3-5)
- AZF Seating, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Dinner, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Program Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Program Artists and Speakers, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Program Data, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 10-11)
- Music Festival, Foster Hall, February 23, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Israel Trip, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Israel Tours, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Films, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
- Akron, Ohio, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
- Altoona, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
- Beaver Falls, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 7-8)
- Brownsville, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 9-10)
- Butler, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 11-12)
- Canton, Ohio, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 13-14)
- Charleston, W.Va, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 15-16)
- East Liverpool, Ohio, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 17-18)
- Erie, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 19-20)
- Greensburg, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 21-22)
- Huntington, W.Va., 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 23-24)
- Indiana, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 25-26)
- Johnstown, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 27-28)
- New Castle, Ellwood City, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 29-30)
- New Kensington, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 31-32)
- Sharon, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
- Steubenville, Ohio, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
- Warren, Ohio, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
- Washington, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 7-8)
- Wheeling, W.Va., 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 9-10)
- Uniontown, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 11-12)
- Youngstown, Ohio Membership Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Youngstown, Ohio Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Executive Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Irwin Stahl, ZOA Comptroller, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Youth Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Region Youth Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Executive Committee Region Officers, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Irwin Stahl, ZOA Comptroller, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Membership Reports- Region, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Dr. Morris A. Landes, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Membership Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Membership Billings, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Conferences, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Conferences Regional Correspondence Mailings, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- M.A. Golomb, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Key Leaders Mailings, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Leadership Names, Region, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Membership, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- AZF Data, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- NEC and National Officers, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- New York Releases, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Independent Zionists, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- American Zionist Council, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Political Development, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Membership Billings, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Program and Education Manual, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Israel Information, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Hebrew Lessons, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Hebrew at Home, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Hebrew Day School, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Hebrew Language and Cultural Depts, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Books, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Youth Commission, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Young Zionist District, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Condolences and Recovery, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Changes of Address, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Congratulations, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Kfar Silver, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- ZOA House, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- AZF Welfare Fund, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Photos Lent Out, 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Leon Illutovitch Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 2)
- A. Flitman (Box 68, Folder 3)
- J.B. Berstein (Box 68, Folder 4)
- H.H. Kimel (Box 68, Folder 5)
- AZF Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Executive Committee Lists (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Board Pending (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Board of Directors Meeting Attendance (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Board Dinner (Box 68, Folder 10)
- A. Flitman (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Board Minutes and Agendas (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Executive Committee Agendas, Meetings, Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Board Correspondence (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Nominations Committee (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Special Membership Committee (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Zionist Council Lists (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Membership Data, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Membership Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Membership Mailings to Workers, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Membership Count by Zones, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Membership Statistics, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Membership Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Membership Billings Reminder, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Membership Annual Statistics, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Membership Billings, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Membership Mailings by Workers, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Membership Kickoff, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Congratulations, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Membership Awards, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Membership Statistics, lists, Attendance, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Mrs. Flitman Membership Lists, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Membership Campaign Closing Dinner, 1961-1962 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Budget, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Financial Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Advance and Duplicate Dues, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- AZF Income, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Jewish National Fund, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- AZF Seating, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Bonds, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Bonds- Dinner, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- AZF Kickoff, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Fund Drive, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 10-11)
- AZF Mailings to Workers, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- AZF Lists, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- AZF Kickoff, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- AZF Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Jacob Wolk Letter, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- AZF Program, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- AZF Unpaid, 1961-1962 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Conference, 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Conventions, 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Regional Conferences Kit, 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Meetings, Conventions, 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Convention, 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Annual Meeting, 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- N.Y. Releases, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- N.E.C. and National Officers, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- American Zionist Council, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Aliyah Folder, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Advance to National, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Political Development, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Israel Information, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Books, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Baskind Memorial, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Education, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Kfar Silver Photos, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Kfar Silver Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Changes of Address, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- Condolences and Recovery, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- David Lowenthal, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Cultural, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Purim Dance, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Program Data, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Program Symposium, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Program Music Festival, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Program Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Films, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Israel Tours, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Publicity, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- AZF Data, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- AZF Mailings to Prospects, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- AZF Income, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Political Developments, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Program Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- N.Y. Releases, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Nominations Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Near East Report Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- N.E.C. and National Officers, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- AZF Mailings to Workers, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Membership Closing Dinner, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Program Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Program Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Purim Dance, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Program Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Program Music Festival, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Purim Dance, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Program Data, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Publicity, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Reservations and Checks, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Picnic Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Program Music Festival, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Tax Receipts, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- U.J.F., 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Youth Commission Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Synagogue Relations, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- ZOA House, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Young Zionist District, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Zionist Council Lists, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Israel Anniversary, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Zionist Council Anniversary Program Ticket Sales, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Anniversary Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Israel Anniversary, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Zionist Council Anniversary Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Zionist Council Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Annual Meeting, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- A. Flitman, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- AZF Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- AZF, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Baskind Memorial, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Board Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Board Dinner, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Board Pending, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Bonds, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Bond Dinner, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Board of Directors, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Books, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Congratulations, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Condolence and Recovery, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- ZOA Convention, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Convention- National, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Cultural Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Education, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Executive Committee Correspondence, Agenda, Meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Executive Committee Lists, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Financial Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- Films, 1962-1963 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- A. Flitman, 1963-1963 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- H.H. Kimel, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Samuel Saul, Jr., 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Advance and Duplicate Dues, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- AZF Lists Dinner, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- AZF Data, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- AZF Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Advance to National, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- AZF Lists, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- AZF Program Book, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- AZF Seating, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Membership Lists, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Membership Report Meetings, Statistics, Lists, Attendance, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Aliyah, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- AZF Kickoff, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- H.H. Kimel AZF, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 16)
- American-Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- American Zionist Council, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- AZF Unpaid, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Baskind Memorial Fund, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Membership Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Membership Reminder Billings, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Membership Mailings by Workers, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Membership Statistics, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Membership Campaign Comments, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Conference Region, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- M.A. Paul, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Conference Region H.H. Kimel, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Region Conference Reservations, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Region Conference, June 21, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Conference Kit, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Altoona, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Brownsville, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Butler, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Charleston, W.Va., 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Erie, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- Greensburg, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Indiana, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Johnstown, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- New Castle, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- New Kensington, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Sharon, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Uniontown, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Washington, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Huntington, W.Va., 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Wheeling, W.Va., 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Akron, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Steubenville, Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Warren, Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Youngstown, Ohio Membership, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Youngstown, Ohio Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Regional Conference, Sharon, November 10, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Joseph Hill, President, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Minutes, Region Meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Region Membership, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Officers, Region, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- Pending Region, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 17)
- Region Executive Meeting, August 18, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Uniontown Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Young Adult Zionists Region, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 20)
- Youth Commission Region, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 21)
- Regional Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 22)
- Region Conference Planning, June 23, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Installation Dinner, February 16, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Region Conference, June 24, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- H.H. Kimel File- Regional Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Region Conference, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Membership, AZF Statistics, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Membership Billings, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Regional Officers, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Dr. Morris A. Landes, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Irwin Stahl, ZOA Comptroller, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Region Youth Commission, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Membership Campaign, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Altoona, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Beaver Falls, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Brownsville, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Butler, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Erie, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Greensburg, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Indiana, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Johnstown, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- New Castle, Ellwood City, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- New Kensington, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Sharon, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Uniontown, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Warren, PA, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Washington, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Charleston, W.VA., 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Huntington, W.VA., 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Wheeling, W.VA., 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- Akron, Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Steubenville, Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Canton, Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Warren, Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Youngstown, Ohio, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 24-25)
- H.H. Kimel, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Samuel Saul, Jr., 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Aliyah, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- American-Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- American Jewish Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Responses to Letters of Si Silverman, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Board of Directors Meeting Attendance, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Board Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Board Lists, District and Region, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- A. Flitman, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Board Minutes and Agendas, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Board Officers, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Board Pending, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Bonds- Bond Transfer Forms, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Bond Dinner, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- AZF- H.H. Kimel, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- A. Flitman- Seating, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- AZF Campaign Tickets, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- AZF Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- AZF Data, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- AZF- H.H. Kimel, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- AZF Kickoff, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- AZF Mailings, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 23)
- AZF Mailings to Workers, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- AZF Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- AZF Income, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- AZF Lists, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- AZF Program Book, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- AZF Seating, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- AZF Unpaid, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Annual Meeting, May 28, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Annual Meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Program Book, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Books, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Bulletin, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- May Bulletin, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Calendar Events, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Car Expenses, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Congratulations, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Condolence and Recovery, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Convention, October 1, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Convention National ZOA, 1963-1964 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Changes of Address, 1963-1964 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- ZOA Convention, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- National Convention, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Cultural Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Education, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Pittsburgh Zionist Council, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Executive Committee Correspondence, Agendas, Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Executive Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 4-5)
- Financial Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Hospitalization, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Hillel Academy, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Interfaith, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Israel Tours, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Jewish National Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Kfar Silver Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Membership Awards, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Membership Billings, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Membership Kickoff, 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Membership Campaign Comments, 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Membership Clean-Up Campaign, 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Membership Closing Dinner, 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Membership Data, 1963-1964 (Box 89, Folder 5-7)
- Membership Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Program Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Program Meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Program Data, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Program Music Festival, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Membership, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Publicity, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Purim Dance, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 8-9)
- Tax Receipts, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Tours, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Zionist Council, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- ZOA House, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Youth Commission Data, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Youth Commission Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Young Zionist District, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Zionist Council Lists, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Zionist Council Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Captains' Reports, Membership Drive, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Tri-State Zionist League Membership, 1964-1965 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Pittsburgh District Membership, 1964-1965 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Unpaid Membership List, January 22, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Membership List, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Pittsburgh Zionist Publication- Pittsburgh Zionist (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Campaign Comments/Briefs (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Campaign Clippings (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Bulletin, 1958-1959 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- ACPA Newsletter (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Israel Digest (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Near East Report (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Jewish Agency's Digest of Press and Events (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Jewish Community Relations Council Bulletin (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Jewish Pictorial Leader (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Looking Ahead (Box 95, Folder 4)
- ZINS (Box 95, Folder 5-6)
- ZOA House News (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Publications (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Zionist Organization of America Conventions Memoranda and Brochures, 1947-1959; 1947-1949 (Box 96, Folder 1)